A Guide to the Smithey & Boynton, Architects & Engineers Records, 1922-1985
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series II: Project Files and Drawings, 1923-1985
  - #497 - Plank, Floyd building, College Avenue, Blacksburg, VA, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 7, Box-folder Oversize box, Folder Folder 4, Box 41)
  - #498 - North Austinville School (Wythe County, VA), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - #502 - Oakland School Grading Playground (Roanoke, VA), 1939 (Box 7, Folder 9, Box 41)
  - #504 - Webster Brick Company (Webster, VA),, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - #505 - Greenwood, W.E. residence (Roanoke, VA), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 11, Box 41)
  - #506 - West, E.E. residence (Roanoke, VA), 1939 (Box 7, Folder 12, Box 41)
  - #507 - Town of Lexington - Dold residence inspection, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - #508 - Morris Plan Bank, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 14, Box 41)
  - #509 - Hobbie Brothers Store -Alterations (Roanoke, VA) (Box 41)
  - #510 - Colonial American Bank Building (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - #512 - Malcolm, C.B office buildings (Roanoke, VA), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 17, Box 41)
  - #513 - Winchester Armory, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 18, Box 41)
  - #514 - Shenandoah Life Building, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 19, Box 41)
  - #514a - Shenandoah Life Building - Elevators, 1939-1941 (Box 7, Folder 20, Box 41)
  - #515 - Lunsford, Kirk residence, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 21, Box 41)
  - #516 - Covington National Bank, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 22, Box 42)
  - #518 - Morris Plan Bank - banking screens, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - #520 - Smithey, Nellie residence (Roanoke, VA), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 24, Box 42)
  - #522 - Wampler, Rev. French residence (Bridle Creek, VA), 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - #523 - Auto Spring and Bearing Company (Roanoke, VA), 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - #524 - Roanoke Armory - alterations, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 27, Box 42)
  - #525 - Lindsey - Robinson office alterations (Roanoke, VA), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - #526 - Town of Wytheville, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - #527 - Paxton, M.W. residence - alterations and additions (Lexington, VA), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - #528 - Fitzpatrick, Earl A. residence (Roanoke, VA), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 31, Box 42)
  - #529 - Lewis Gale Hospital, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 32, Box 42)
  - #530 - Re-Nu Cleaners - Jakra, Philip (Roanoke, VA), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 33, Box 42)
  - #531 - All Saints Episcopal Church - Rectory (Norton, VA), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - #532 - Hamlin, Fred E. residence (Roanoke County, VA), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 35, Box 42)
  - #534 - Neal, E. Berkley Residence (Roanoke, VA) (Box 42)
  - #537 - City of Roanoke stadium, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - #538 - Boy's Home, Inc. - chapel (Covington, VA), 1942 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - #539 - Stoker installation for four residences (Roanoke County, VA), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - #543 - Kline Corporation Building and Alterations (Norton, VA), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 39, Box 42)
  - #544 - Cocke, Estes residence (Hollins, VA), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 40, Box 42)
  - #545 - Waldrop, Mrs. A.A. residence, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 41, Box 42)
  - #555 - Davis, J.W. residence (Roanoke, VA), 1940 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - #561 - Bus Storage Building - Safety Motor Corporation (Roanoke, VA), 1941-1942 (Box 7, Folder 43, Box 42)
  - #566 - Armory Survey - Virginia State Planning Board, 1940-1942 (Box 7, Folder 44, Box 42)
  - #567 - Morris Plan Bank - dumb waiter (Roanoke, VA), 1941 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - #569 - National Bank of Blacksburg building, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 46, Folder Project #569 - National Bank of Blacksburg)
  - #571 - First National Exchange Bank (Roanoke, VA), 1942-1946 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - #572 - Loving, R.V. funeral home alterations (Covington, VA), 1941-1945 (Box 7, Folder 48, Box 42)
  - #573 - West Virginia Pulp & Paper Company - office addition (Covington, VA), 1941-1949 (Box 7, Folder 49, Box 42)
  - #574 - Johnson, Gordon E. residence alterations (Roanoke, VA), 1941 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - #576 - Garden, H.R. residence - porch (Salem, VA) (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - #578 - Proposed Defence Schools (Montgomery County, VA), 1941-1951 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - #579 - Nettleton, C.B. Store Building (Covington, VA), 1941 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - #580 - Covington High School,, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 2, Box 42)
  - #581 - Roanoke Vocational School,, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - #583 - Shenandoah Life Insurance, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - #584 - Burton, C.T. residence, 1941-1950 (Box 8, Folder 5, Box 42)
  - #585 - Williams, Dr. M.H. residence (Roanoke, VA), 1941 (Box 8, Folder 6, Box 42)
  - #586 - Hamilton, John W. residence (Martinsville, VA), 1941 (Box 8, Folder 7, Box 42)
  - #587 - Davis, J.W. residence (Catawba, VA), 1941 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - #588 - U.S.O. Recreation Building (Radford, VA), 1941-1949 (Box 8, Folder 9-10, Box 42)
  - #589 - Peck, H. Crim residence (Lexington, VA), 1941 (Box 8, Folder 11, Box 42)
  - #590 - Roanoke Country Club,, 1941-1950 (Box 8, Folder 12-14, Box 42)
  - #591 - First National Exchange Bank (Roanoke, VA), 1941 (Box 8, Folder 15, Box 42)
  - #592 - Roanoke Hospital, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - #593 - Montgomery, T.E. residence (Roanoke, VA), 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - #594 - Wallace, A.W. residence (Roanoke, VA), 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 18, Box 42)
  - #595 - Sands and Company (Roanoke, VA), 1941 (Box 8, Folder 19, Box 42)
  - #596 - Misser, J.A. Jr. residence (Galax, VA), 1941-1943 (Box 8, Folder 20, Box 42)
  - #597 - Higgins, C.W. Jr. residence (Galax, VA), 1941-1968 (Box 8, Folder 21-23, Box 42)
  - #598 - Dickerson, E.M. residence (Roanoke, VA), 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 24, Box 42)
  - #599 - Twyman residence (Fincastle, VA), 1941-1948 (Box 8, Folder 25, Box 42)
  - #600 - Smith, L.E. residence (Roanoke, VA) (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - #601 - Stone, K.D. heating plant (Fincastle, VA), 1941 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - #603 - White, I.G. apartments (Salem, VA), 1941 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - #604 - White Foundry Company shed (Roanoke, VA) (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - #611 - Terminal Mundy Motor Lines (Christiansburg, VA), 1942 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - #612 - Mundy Motor Lines garage (Roanoke, VA), 1945 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - #614 - Kline, F.B. store (Norton, VA), 1945 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - #615 - First National Exchange Bank (Roanoke, VA), 1945 (Box 8, Folder 33, Box 42)
  - #618 - Noland Company Inc. warehouse (Roanoke, VA), 1948-1959 (Box 8, Folder 34-36, Box 42)
  - #622 - Industrial Rayon Corporation (Cleveland, OH), 1945-1948 (Box 9, Folder 1-5, Box 42)
  - #623 - Double Envelope Corporation - Addition (Roanoke, VA), 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - #624 - Roanoke City Mills - Consulting, 1945-1947 (Box 9, Folder 7, Box 43)
  - #625 - Wytheville High School (Wythe County, VA), 1946-1952 (Box 9, Folder 8, Box 43)
  - #626 - Wilkerson, L.G. Garage and Showroom (Roanoke, VA), 1945 (Box 9, Folder 9, Box 43)
  - #629 - Huff, Leigh residence (Roanoke, VA), 1945 (Box 9, Folder 10, Box 43)
  - #630 - Roanoke City Mills Inc. - Heating Plant,, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 11, Box 43)
  - #631 - Mills, Ralph warehouse building (Salem, VA), 1945 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - #636 - Shenandoah Life Insurance Company (Roanoke, VA), 1945-1946 (Box 9, Folder 13, Box 43)
  - #638 - Senter, E.W. residence (Salem, VA) (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - #640 - Trinity Episcopal Church (Rocky Mount, VA), 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 15, Box 43)
  - #641 - Armory for the City of Roanoke - Stadium location (Roanoke, VA), 1947-1952 (Box 9, Folder 16-17)
  - #642 - Radford High School - Additions, 1947-1954 (Box 9, Folder 18-20, Box 43)
  - #642a - Radford High School - Additions (Radford, VA), 1951-1955 (Box 9, Folder 21-22)
  - #643 - Cinder Block Incorporated (Roanoke, VA), 1945-1947 (Box 9, Folder 23, Box 43)
  - #644 - Critz - Remodeling (Salem, VA), 1945-1947 (Box 9, Folder 24, Box 43)
  - #645 - YWCA Girl Scout Camp (Montgomery County, VA), 1938-1946 (Box 9, Folder 25, Box 43)
  - #650 - Central Manufacturing Company - Warehouse (Roanoke, VA), 1945-1946 (Box 9, Folder 26, Box 43)
  - #651 - Booth, G.W. residence (Franklin County, VA), 1946 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - #652 - Franklin Theatre (Rocky Mount, VA), 1945-1947 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - #653 - Mount Theatre (Rocky Mount, VA), 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - #657 - Wytheville Training School, 1945-1953 (Box 10, Folder 4-8, Box 43)
  - #659 - Forman, Isadore swimming pool (Roanoke, VA), 1945 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - #662 - Davis and Stephenson Building (Roanoke, VA), 1946-1948 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - #663 - G & H Coach Line (Norton, VA), 1945 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - #664 - Waynesboro Junior High School, 1946-1958 (Box 10, Folder 12-13, Box 43)
  - #665 - Hannabas, Howard residence (Roanoke, VA), 1946 (Box 10, Folder 14, Box 43)
  - #666 - Sunnyside Awning and Tent Company (Roanoke, VA), 1946-1950 (Box 10, Folder 15, Box 43)
  - #667 - B.F. Parrott and Company garage building (Roanoke, VA), 1945-1946 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - #668 - S & W Cafeteria (Roanoke, VA), 1936 (Box 10, Folder 17-18, Box 43)
  - #669 - Toddle House (Roanoke, VA), 1946 (Box 10, Folder 19, Box 43)
  - #670 - Carden, B.J., Jr. residence (Roanoke, VA), 1946 (Box 10, Folder 20, Box 43)
  - #671 - Dickey, Paul O. residence (Roanoke, VA), 1945 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - #672 - Norfolk and Western Railway Company Storehouse (Roanoke, VA), 1945-1957 (Box 10, Folder 22-25, Box 43)
  - #673 - Norman Shepherd Incorporated (Roanoke, VA), 1946-1947 (Box 11, Folder 1, Box 43)
  - #674 - Cinder Block Incorporated, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - #675 - St. John's Episcopal Church (Roanoke, VA), 1946-1953 (Box 11, Folder 3, Box 43)
  - #675a - St. John's Episcopal Church - Parish House (Roanoke, VA), 1948-1949 (Box 11, Folder 4, Box 43)
  - #676 - Bailey, H. - Proposed Theatre (Rural Retreat, VA), 1946 (Box 11, Folder 5, Box 43)
  - #677 - Blacksburg Development Corporation (Blacksburg, VA), 1946-1948 (Box 11, Folder 6, Box 43)
  - #678 - First Church of the Brethren (Roanoke, VA), 1947-1948 (Box 11, Folder 7-8, Box 43)
  - #679 - William P. Swartz Jr. and Company (Roanoke, VA), 1946 (Box 11, Folder 9, Box 43)
  - #680 - Alleghany Company Incorporated (Clifton Forge, VA), 1946 (Box 11, Folder 10, Box 43)
  - #681 - New Vogue Cleaners and Dryers (Roanoke, VA), 1946 (Box 11, Folder 11, Box 43)
  - #682 - Maher Field - Baseball Stand (Roanoke, VA), 1945-1946 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - #683 - Dam and Reservoir for Thaden-Jorden Corporation (Roanoke, VA), 1946 (Box 11, Folder 13, Box 43)
  - #684 - Bowie, Dr. R.C. Apartment Buildings (Galax, VA), 1946-1947 (Box 11, Folder 14, Box 44)
  - #685 - Dublin High School (Pulaski County, VA), 1950-1959 (Box 11, Folder 15-17, Box 44)
  - #686 - Berryville Elementary School, 1946-1947 (Box 11, Folder 18, Box 44)
  - #686a - Berryville Elementary School, 1948-1950 (Box 11, Folder 19, Box 44)
  - #687 - Hart, J.P. Jr. Apartments (Roanoke, VA) (Box 11, Folder 20, Box 44)
  - #688 - Tinker Creek Elementary School (Roanoke, VA), 1946-1948 (Box 11, Folder 21, Box 44)
  - #689 - Winchester Jail (Frederick County, VA), 1948-1965 (Box 11, Folder 22-23, Box 44)
  - #689 - Winchester Jail (Frederick County, VA), 1942-1949 (Box 12, Folder 1, Box 44)
  - #689a - Winchester Jail (Frederick County, VA), 1948-1964 (Box 12, Folder 2, Box 44)
  - #690 - Nelson Hardware Company (Roanoke, VA), 1946-1947 (Box 12, Folder 3, Box 44)
  - #691 - Christiansburg Industrial Institute - property valuation (Montgomery County, VA), 1946-1951 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - #692 - Ring, M.F. Duplex house (Roanoke, VA), 1946 (Box 12, Folder 5, Box 44)
  - #693 - Industrial Rayon Corporation (Covington, VA), 1947-1949 (Box 12, Folder 6-10, Box 44)
  - #694 - Mills, Ralph residence (Roanoke, VA), 1946 (Box 12, Folder 11, Box 44)
  - #695 - Kelley, J.H. Jr. residence (Roanoke, VA), 1946-1947 (Box 12, Folder 12, Box 44)
  - #696 - Sprinkle, Vivian residence (Roanoke, VA), 1946 (Box 12, Folder 13, Box 44)
  - #697 - Williams, Mrs. Crawley residence (Covington, VA), 1946 (Box 12, Folder 14, Box 44)
  - #698 - Boden, D.W. residence (Galax, VA), 1946 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - #699 - Nelson Hardware Company warehouse shed (Roanoke, VA), 1947 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - #701 - Richlands High School (Tazewell County, VA), 1946-1958 (Box 12, Folder 17-19, Box 44)
  - #702 - Cedar Bluff Elementary School (Tazewell County, VA), 1951-1952 (Box 12, Folder 20, Box 44)
  - #702a - Cedar Bluff Elementary School (Tazewell County, VA), 1952-1955 (Box 12, Folder 21, Box 44)
  - #703 - Richlands Elementary School (Tazewell County, VA), 1946-1948 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - #704 - Big Rock Elementary School (Buchanan County, VA), 1946-1951 (Box 12, Folder 23, Box 45)
  - #705 - Harmon Elementary School (Buchanan County, VA), 1950-1954 (Box 12, Folder 24-25, Box 45)
  - #706 - Vansant Elementary School (Buchanan County, VA), 1951-1953 (Box 13, Folder 1-2, Box 45)
  - #707 - Grundy Elementary School (Buchanan County, VA), 1950-1952 (Box 13, Folder 3-4, Box 45)
  - #708 - Garden High School and Garden Elementary School (Buchanan County, VA), 1946-1958 (Box 13, Folder 5, Box 45)
  - #708a - Garden Elementary School (Buchanan County, VA), 1953-1954 (Box 13, Folder 6, Box 45)
  - #709 - Hurley High School (Buchanan County, VA), 1953-1954 (Box 13, Folder 7-8, Box 45)
  - #710 - Whitehood High School (Buchanan County, VA), 1946-1980, 1946-1958 (Box 13, Folder 9-11, Box 45)
  - #711 - North Pulaski Primary School, 1948-1952 (Box 13, Folder 12, Box 45)
  - #712 - Rogers Hall Boys Home (Covington, VA), 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13, Box 45)
  - #713 - Fairlawn Elementary School (Pulaski County, VA), 1947-1950 (Box 13, Folder 14, Box 45)
  - #714 - Pulaski High School (Pulaski County, VA), 1951-1967 (Box 13, Folder 15, Box 14, Folder 1-7, Box 45)
  - #715 - Claremont Elementary School (Pulaski County, VA), 1950-1957 (Box 14, Folder 8-9, Box 46)
  - #716 - Ewing Elementary School (Lee County, VA), 1946-1948 (Box 14, Folder 10, Box 46)
  - #717 - Flatwoods High School (Lee County, VA), 1946 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - #718 - Plank and Stoner - apartment alterations (Blacksburg, VA), 1946-1947 (Box 14, Folder 12, Box 46)
  - #719 - Neuhoff, Lorenz Jr. residence (Roanoke, VA), 1946-1948 (Box 14, Folder 13, Box 46)
  - #720 - Wirsing residence (Roanoke, VA), 1946 (Box 14, Folder 14, Box 46)
  - #721 - Williams, Mrs. John W. residence (Roanoke, VA), 1946 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - #722 - First National Exchange Bank (Roanoke, VA), 1946 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - #723 - Williams, Lucy Henry residence - Alterations to Sam P. Weems residence (Roanoke, VA), 1946 (Box 14, Folder 17, Box 46)
  - #724 - Crystal Spring Laundry and Dry Cleaners (Roanoke, VA), 1946-1949 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - #725 - Rocky Mount High School (Rocky Mount, VA), 1948-1955 (Box 14, Folder 19-20)
  - #726 - Seven-Up Bottling Company (Roanoke, VA), 1946 (Box 14, Folder 21, Box 46)
  - #727 - Safety Motor Transit Company (Roanoke, VA), 1946 (Box 15, Folder 1, Box 46)
  - #728 - Countess Cittadini residence (Hot Springs, VA), 1946 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - #729 - Virginia Tractor Company (Roanoke, VA), 1946-1947 (Box 14, Folder 22, Box 46)
  - #730 - Pollard Taxi Company (Roanoke, VA), 1946 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - #732 - Holland, Mrs. Lane residence (Roanoke, VA), 1946 (Box 15, Folder 4, Box 46)
  - #733 - Weber City Elementary School, 1947-1952 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - #734 - Gate City High School (Scott County, VA), 1945-1953 (Box 15, Folder 6, Box 46)
  - #736 - Dungannon High School - proposed gymnasium (Scott County, VA), 1947-1949 (Box 15, Folder 7, Box 46)
  - #737 - Stone Printing Company (Roanoke, VA), 1946-1954 (Box 15, Folder 8, Box 46)
  - #738 - Covington High School - Home Economics Building (Covington, VA), 1946 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - #739 - Stone, Mrs. Edward residence (Roanoke, VA), 1946 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - #740 - Walker Foundry and Machine Company (Roanoke, VA), 1946-1947 (Box 15, Folder 11, Box 46)
  - #741 - Dunlap School - Additions (Alleghany County, VA), 1946-1947 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - #742 - Boiling Spring School - Additions (Alleghany County, VA), 1946-1948 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - #743 - Walters, Francis residence (Salem, VA), 1946 (Box 15, Folder 14, Box 46)
  - #745 - Twyman, Lewis residence (Buckingham County, VA), 1946-1955 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - #746 - Moore, Franklin residence (Roanoke, VA), 1946-1950 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - #747 - Honaker High School (Russell County, VA), 1950-1960 (Box 15, Folder 17-19, Box 46)
  - #748 - Castlewood High School (Castlewood, VA), 1946-1956 (Box 15, Folder 20-21, Box 47)
  - #749 - Steger Pharmacy (Covington, VA), 1946-1947 (Box 15, Folder 22, Box 47)
  - #750 - Christiansburg Presbyterian Church (Christiansburg, VA), 1946-1947 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - #751 - Ulmer residence (Roanoke, VA), 1947 (Box 15, Folder 24, Box 47)
  - #752 - Winchester City Hall, 1947-1955 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - #753 - Baywood Elementary School (Grayson County, VA), 1947-1955 (Box 15, Folder 26-27, Box 47)
  - #754 - St. Paul Consolidated Elementary School (Carroll County, VA), 1948-1957 (Box 15, Folder 28, Box 47)
  - #755 - Shenandoah Life Insurance Company (Roanoke, VA), 1948-1956 (Box 15, Folder 29-30, Box 16, Folder 1, Box 47)
  - #756 - Low Moor School additions (Alleghany County, VA), 1946 (Box 16, Folder 2, Box 48)
  - #757 - Roanoke Rock Wool Company, 1946-1947 (Box 16, Folder 3, Box 47)
  - #758 - C. Carter Lee law offices (Rocky Mount, VA), 1946-1947 (Box 16, Folder 4, Box 47)
  - #759 - Methodist Church alterations (Bridle Creek, VA), 1947-1950 (Box 16, Folder 5, Box 47)
  - #760 - Roanoke City Mills,, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 6, Box 47)
  - #761 - Dr. John H. Stoke residence alterations (Roanoke, VA), 1946-1948 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - #762 - Manassas Technical School (Prince William County, VA), 1945-1950 (Box 16, Folder 8, Box 47)
  - #763 - First National Bank of Roanoke, 1939-1948 (Box 16, Folder 9, Box 47)
  - #764 - Twin County Motor Company, 1946-1950 (Box 16, Folder 10, Box 47)
  - #765 - Saint Paul's Episcopal Church, 1947-1954 (Box 16, Folder 11, Box 47)
  - #766 - Lebanon Elementary School (Russell County, VA), 1954-1963 (Box 16, Folder 12-15, Box 47)
  - #768 - Colonial American National Bank (Roanoke, VA), 1948-1949 (Box 16, Folder 16-19, Box 47)
  - #769 - Cattle Sales Building, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 20, Box 48)
  - #770 - Christiansburg High School (Montgomery County, VA), 1948-1949 (Box 16, Folder 21, Box 48)
  - #771 - Shawsville High School (Montgomery County, VA), 1947-1948 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - #772 - New Vogue Cleaners and Dyers (Roanoke, VA), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 2, Box 48)
  - #773 - Manassas Regional High School, 1947-1949 (Box 17, Folder 3-4, Box 48)
  - #774 - First National Exchange Bank, 1947-1952 (Box 17, Folder 5, Box 48)
  - #775 - J.H. Pence Store Alterations, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - #776 - First National Bank (Martinsville, VA) (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - #778 - Second Presbyterian Church (Roanoke, VA), 1947-1958 (Box 17, Folder 8, Box 48)
  - #779 - Harry Rosenbaum Warehouse (Roanoke, VA), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 9, Box 48)
  - #780 - Thorton-Creasy Store Remodeling (Roanoke,VA), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 10, Box 48)
  - #781 - WSLS FM station (Poor Mountain), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 11, Box 48)
  - #782 - Residence - Washington Avenue and Third Street SW (Roanoke, VA), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 12, Box 48)
  - #783 - Mission House - Episcopal (St. Paul, VA), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - #784 - Evans House - Diocese of Southwestern Virginia, 1947-1951 (Box 17, Folder 14, Box 48)
  - #785 - Francis H. Barnes residence (Roanoke, VA), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 15, Box 48)
  - #786 - Caldwell Sites Company warehouse building (Vinton, VA), 1947-1950 (Box 17, Folder 16, Box 48)
  - #787 - Roanoke Photo Finishing Company - camera shop lighting, 1946-1948 (Box 17, Folder 17, Box 48)
  - #788 - Roy Pollard swimming pool (Roanoke, VA), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - #789 - Allison Gap School (Smyth County, VA), 1947-1948 (Box 17, Folder 19, Box 48)
  - #790 - Leigh Huff Store building (Roanoke, VA), 1947-1948 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - #791 - Spring Valley Elementary School (Grayson County, VA), 1951-1954 (Box 17, Folder 21-22, Box 48)
  - #792 - Bridle Creek School (Grayson County, VA), 1947-1951 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - #793 - Draper School (Pulaski County, VA), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - #794 - G. Ernest Brown residence (Roanoke, VA), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - #795 - Bassett Chair Company (Bassett, VA), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - #796 - Mrs. Edgar Funkhouser residence - heating modernization (Roanoke, VA), 1947-1950 (Box 17, Folder 27, Box 48)
  - #797 - Cinder Block, Inc. (Roanoke, VA), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 28, Box 48)
  - #798 - Methodist Church - alterations (Stuart, VA), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 29, Box 48)
  - #799 - Walker Machine & Foundry Corporation (Roanoke, VA), 1947-1953 (Box 17, Folder 30, Box 48)
  - #800 - Rose's Store alterations (Floyd, VA), 1947-1948 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - #801 - Norfolk & Western railway passenger station (Christiansburg, VA), 1947-1948 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - #802 - Woodrow Wilson Junior High School (Roanoke, VA), 1947-1953 (Box 17, Folder 33-37, Box 18, Folder 1, Box 48)
  - #803 - WSLS Studio alterations (Roanoke, VA), 1947 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - #804 - J.W. Ring residence (Roanoke, VA), 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 3, Box 48)
  - #805 - Fairview Elementary School (Grayson County, VA), 1947-1951 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - #806 - Yale and Towne Plant (Salem, VA), 1947-1950 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - #807 - Mt. Rogers Elementary School (Grayson County, VA), 1950-1954 (Box 18, Folder 6, Box 48)
  - #808 - Independence High School, 1947-1948 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - #809 - Flatridge School (Grayson County, VA), 1950-1954 (Box 18, Folder 8, Box 49)
  - #810 - Virginia Holding Corporation garage and laundry - Norfolk and Western Railway (Roanoke, VA), 1947-1949 (Box 18, Folder 9-10, Box 49)
  - #812 - Double Envelope Corporation (Roanoke, VA), 1937-1948 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - #813 - Consolidated Colored High School (Warrenton, VA), 1948-1954 (Box 18, Folder 12-15, Box 49)
  - #814 - Roanoke City Mills - molasses tank, 1948-1955 (Box 18, Folder 16, Box 49)
  - #815 - Roanoke Water Department pumping station, 1947-1948 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - #816 - Rocky Mount Colored School - home economics unit, 1947-1948 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - #817 - Webster Brick Company (Roanoke, VA), 1947-1949 (Box 18, Folder 19, Box 49)
  - #818 - Blacksburg High School - vocational unit, 1949-1959 (Box 18, Folder 20-21, Box 49)
  - #818a - Blacksburg High School, 1951-1961 (Box 18, Folder 22-25, Box 49)
  - #819 - Valley Roofing Corporation - B.F. Parrott & Co. (Roanoke, VA), 1948` (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - #820 - Martinsville Schools - consulting, 1948-1949 (Box 19, Folder 2-3, Box 50)
  - #821 - Lambsburg School addition (Carroll County, VA), 1948 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - #822 - Vaughan Schools addition (Carroll County, VA), 1948 (Box 19, Folder 5, Box 50)
  - #823 - Sylvatus School additions (Carroll County, VA), 1948-1953 (Box 19, Folder 6-7, Box 50)
  - #824 - Price's Fork Elementary School (Montgomery County, VA), 1951-1953 (Box 19, Folder 8-9, Box 50)
  - #825 - Wright Motor Co. paving for parking lot (Roanoke, VA), 1948 (Box 19, Folder 10, Box 50)
  - #826 - Galax Elementary School, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - #827 - Whitlock, Mrs. P.C. pool alterations, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 12, Box 50)
  - #828 - Dante Elementary School (Russell County, VA), 1948-1953 (Box 19, Folder 13-14, Box 50)
  - #829 - Swartz, William P. warehouse (Roanoke, VA), 1948 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - #830 - Hall, Mrs. Harvey residence (Roanoke, VA), 1948-1949 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - #831 - Christiansburg High School shop addition (Montgomery County, VA), 1948 (Box 19, Folder 17, Box 50)
  - #832 - Franklin County Training School, 1948-1949 (Box 19, Folder 18, Box 50)
  - #833 - Methodist Church alterations and additions (Christiansburg, VA), 1948 (Box 19, Folder 19, Box 50)
  - #835 - First National Exchange Bank (Roanoke, VA), 1948-1953 (Box 19, Folder 20-23, Box 50)